[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bea"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "किसे दिल्ली जाना है?",
  "options": [
    "मैं",
    "तुम",
    "वह",
    "हम"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "मैं"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998beb"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "राम के पास कितनी किताबें हैं?",
  "options": [
    "एक",
    "दो",
    "तीन",
    "चार"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "तीन"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bec"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वह कहाँ जा रहा है?",
  "options": [
    "बगीचे",
    "मंदिर",
    "स्कूल",
    "मार्केट"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "स्कूल"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bed"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "इस परीक्षा में कितने छात्र शामिल हैं?",
  "options": [
    "५०",
    "१००",
    "२५०",
    "५००"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "१००"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bee"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "यह कौन सा दिन है?",
  "options": [
    "सोमवार",
    "मंगलवार",
    "बुधवार",
    "शुक्रवार"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "सोमवार"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bef"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "राम किसे पसंद करता है?",
  "options": [
    "मंदिर",
    "पुस्तकें",
    "खेलना",
    "फल"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "पुस्तकें"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf0"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वे क्या खा रहे हैं?",
  "options": [
    "पिज्जा",
    "दाल-चावल",
    "बर्गर",
    "चाय"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "दाल-चावल"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf1"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "किताब क्या है?",
  "options": [
    "कागज",
    "कलम",
    "खेल",
    "पढ़ाई"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "पढ़ाई"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf2"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वे किसे देख रहे हैं?",
  "options": [
    "टीवी",
    "मोबाइल",
    "चिड़िया",
    "सड़क"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "चिड़िया"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf3"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वह किताब कहाँ रखी है?",
  "options": [
    "मेज़",
    "किचन",
    "बेडरूम",
    "बाथरूम"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "बेडरूम"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf4"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "तुम कौन सा गाना गा रहे हो?",
  "options": [
    "क्लासिकल",
    "रॉक",
    "पॉप",
    "गाना नहीं"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "गाना नहीं"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf5"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "कुत्ता कैसे भौंकता है?",
  "options": [
    "मूँदकर",
    "बिना बौंके",
    "डांस करके",
    "दौड़कर"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "बिना बौंके"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf6"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "राजु क्या खेलता है?",
  "options": [
    "कराटे",
    "बास्केटबॉल",
    "फुटबॉल",
    "खूब खेलता है"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "खूब खेलता है"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf7"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "इस छवि में कौन सा फल है?",
  "options": [
    "आम",
    "सेब",
    "केला",
    "अंगूर"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "सेब"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf8"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "कौनसी रंगीन पेड़ी है?",
  "options": [
    "नीला",
    "हरा",
    "लाल",
    "पीला"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "हरा"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bf9"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वह किसे देख रहा है?",
  "options": [
    "टीवी",
    "मोबाइल",
    "किताब",
    "सड़क"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "किताब"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bfa"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "तुम किताब कब पढ़ रहे हो?",
  "options": [
    "सुबह",
    "दोपहर",
    "रात",
    "कभी नहीं"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "रात"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bfb"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "कौन सा पक्षी उड़ता है?",
  "options": [
    "मुर्गा",
    "मेंढ़क",
    "गाय",
    "बतख"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "बतख"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bfc"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वह कहाँ गया था?",
  "options": [
    "शॉपिंग मॉल",
    "बिच",
    "स्कूल",
    "मंदिर"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "स्कूल"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651482b184e0da68e1998bfd"
  },
  "language": "Hindi",
  "question": "वह क्या खा रहा है?",
  "options": [
    "पानी",
    "पिज्जा",
    "संदेश",
    "चाय"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "पिज्जा"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c01"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which of the following is a correct sentence?",
  "options": [
    "She don't like ice cream.",
    "She doesn't like ice cream.",
    "She not likes ice cream.",
    "She not liking ice cream."
  ],
  "correct_answer": "She doesn't like ice cream."
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c02"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the plural form of 'child'?",
  "options": [
    "Childs",
    "Childes",
    "Children",
    "Child's"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Children"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c03"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which word is a synonym for 'happy'?",
  "options": [
    "Sad",
    "Joyful",
    "Angry",
    "Excited"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Joyful"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c04"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which of these words is a preposition?",
  "options": [
    "Run",
    "Quickly",
    "Under",
    "Jump"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Under"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c05"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the past tense of 'eat'?",
  "options": [
    "Eating",
    "Eaten",
    "Ate",
    "Eats"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Ate"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c06"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which of the following is a conjunction?",
  "options": [
    "And",
    "Happy",
    "Quickly",
    "Jumping"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "And"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c07"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the comparative form of 'good'?",
  "options": [
    "Gooder",
    "Better",
    "Best",
    "Goodest"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Better"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c08"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Choose the correct spelling:",
  "options": [
    "Recieve",
    "Receive",
    "Recieive",
    "Recieve"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Receive"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c09"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the superlative form of 'fast'?",
  "options": [
    "Fastest",
    "Faster",
    "Fastly",
    "Fasting"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Fastest"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c0a"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which of these sentences is in the present perfect tense?",
  "options": [
    "She will go to the store.",
    "They went to the park.",
    "He has eaten lunch.",
    "I am reading a book."
  ],
  "correct_answer": "He has eaten lunch."
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c0b"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the plural form of 'mouse'?",
  "options": [
    "Mice",
    "Mouses",
    "Mouse's",
    "Mice's"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Mice"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c0c"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Choose the correct sentence:",
  "options": [
    "Their going to the beach.",
    "They're going to the beach.",
    "There going to the beach.",
    "They going to the beach."
  ],
  "correct_answer": "They're going to the beach."
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c0d"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which of the following is an adverb?",
  "options": [
    "Happy",
    "Slowly",
    "Blue",
    "Jumped"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Slowly"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c0e"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the past participle of 'swim'?",
  "options": [
    "Swimmed",
    "Swam",
    "Swum",
    "Swiming"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Swum"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c0f"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which word is a synonym for 'big'?",
  "options": [
    "Tiny",
    "Huge",
    "Small",
    "Fast"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Huge"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c10"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the antonym of 'dark'?",
  "options": [
    "Light",
    "Shadow",
    "Night",
    "Black"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Light"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c11"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Choose the correct punctuation:",
  "options": [
    "She likes to swim, in the ocean.",
    "She likes to swim in the ocean",
    "She likes to swim in, the ocean.",
    "She likes to swim in the ocean."
  ],
  "correct_answer": "She likes to swim in the ocean."
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c12"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the present continuous form of 'run'?",
  "options": [
    "Running",
    "Run",
    "Ran",
    "Runner"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Running"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c13"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "Which of these words is a pronoun?",
  "options": [
    "Sing",
    "Her",
    "Jump",
    "Quickly"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Her"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "651483de84e0da68e1998c14"
  },
  "language": "English",
  "question": "What is the plural form of 'box'?",
  "options": [
    "Boxs",
    "Boxes",
    "Box's",
    "Boxen"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "Boxes"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c16"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "কোনটি সঠিক বাক্য?",
  "options": [
    "তিনি বই পড়েন না।",
    "তিনি বই পড়ে।",
    "তিনি বই পড়েনই।",
    "তিনি বই পড়েন না।"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "তিনি বই পড়ে।"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c17"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘শিশু’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "শিশুরা",
    "শিশুগণ",
    "শিশুদের",
    "শিশুনি"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "শিশুরা"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c18"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘খুশি’ শব্দের একটি সমানার্থক শব্দ কি?",
  "options": [
    "দু: খিত",
    "আনন্দিত",
    "খুব দু: খিত",
    "দু: খী"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "আনন্দিত"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c19"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘পৃথিবী’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "বুক",
    "লা",
    "কুল",
    "তাল"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "লা"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c1a"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘খাওয়া’ শব্দের মৌলিক রূপ কি?",
  "options": [
    "খে",
    "খাওয়া",
    "খাওয়াই",
    "খায়"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "খাওয়া"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c1b"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘দ্বীপ’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "লা",
    "কুল",
    "গাছ",
    "তাল"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "কুল"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c1c"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘আকাশ’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "কুল",
    "লা",
    "গাছ",
    "তাল"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "গাছ"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c1d"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘তারকা’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "তারকা",
    "তারকারা",
    "তারকাগুলি",
    "তারকাদের"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "তারকাদের"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c1e"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘খাবার’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "খাও",
    "খাবারে",
    "খাওয়া",
    "খাওয়াই"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "খাও"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c1f"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘দাঁত’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "দাঁতেরা",
    "দাঁতগুলি",
    "দাঁতরানি",
    "দাঁতদের"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "দাঁতগুলি"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c20"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘স্কুল’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "স্কুলে",
    "স্কুলগুলি",
    "স্কুলদের",
    "স্কুলের"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "স্কুলের"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c21"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘বাচ্চা’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "বাচ্চা",
    "বাচ্চাগুলি",
    "বাচ্চাদের",
    "বাচ্চাদের"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "বাচ্চাগুলি"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c22"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘প্রদর্শনী’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "প্রদর্শনীরা",
    "প্রদর্শনীর",
    "প্রদর্শনীগুলি",
    "প্রদর্শনীতে"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "প্রদর্শনীর"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c23"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘পুষ্প’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "পুষ্পের",
    "পুষ্পগুলি",
    "পুষ্পেরা",
    "পুষ্পরা"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "পুষ্পগুলি"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c24"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘দুধ’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "দুধটি",
    "দুধের",
    "দুধটির",
    "দুধেরা"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "দুধের"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c25"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘ফুল’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "ফুলেরা",
    "ফুলগুলি",
    "ফুলের",
    "ফুলেরি"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "ফুলগুলি"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c26"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘কবল’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "কবলে",
    "কবলটি",
    "কবলটির",
    "কবলের"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "কবলে"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c27"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘বন্ধু’ শব্দের বহুবচন কি?",
  "options": [
    "বন্ধুরা",
    "বন্ধুদের",
    "বন্ধুগুলি",
    "বন্ধুদেরা"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "বন্ধুগুলি"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6514860084e0da68e1998c28"
  },
  "language": "Bengali",
  "question": "‘খেলা’ শব্দের প্রত্যয় কি?",
  "options": [
    "খেলের",
    "খেলার",
    "খেলা",
    "খেলাই"
  ],
  "correct_answer": "খেলার"
}]